branham.org 2018-12-03

# VGR Privacy Policy

Voice of God Recordings

Privacy Statement

Effective date: **February 23, 2017**

Thank you for entrusting Voice of God Recordings (VGR) with your personal information. We consider this a serious responsibility, and we want you to know how we are handling it.

The short version

We only collect the minimum amount of personal information that is necessary to get the job done. We strive to treat it carefully and to be good stewards of your trust.

Details are below.

Information Voice of God Recordings collects and why

Information from website browsers

If you are just browsing our family of websites, we collect the same basic information that most websites collect. We use common internet technologies, such as cookies and web server logs. This is stuff we collect from everybody, whether they have an account or not.

The information we collect about all visitors to our websites includes the visitor‘s browser type, language preference, referring site, additional websites requested, and the date and time of each visitor request. We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like IP addresses.

Why do we collect this?

We collect this information to better understand how our website visitors use the websites, and to monitor and protect the security of the websites.

Information from users with accounts

If you create an account, we require some basic information at the time of account creation. We will ask you for a valid email account, and other “personal information.”

“Personal information” is any information about one of our users, which could, alone or together with other information, personally identify him or her. Information such as a user name and password, an email address, a real name, and a photograph are examples of “personal information.”

Why do we collect this?

  * We need your personal information to create your account, and to provide services to you.
  * We use it to fill out your profile.
  * We will use your email address or other information to communicate with you.
  * Your privacy is of the utmost importance to VGR, so we limit our use of your personal information to what is required to give you the level of service required.

Our use of Cookies and Tracking

VGR uses cookies to make interactions with our websites easy and meaningful. We use cookies (and similar technologies) to keep you logged in, remember your preferences, and provide information for future development of our web sites.

Certain pages on our site may set other third party cookies. For example, we may embed content, such as videos, from another site that sets a cookie. While we try to minimize these third-party cookies, we cannot always control what cookies this third-party content sets.

Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics as a third-party tracking service, but we don‘t use it to track you individually or collect your personal information. We use Google Analytics to collect information about how our website performs and how our users, in general, use and navigate through our web sites. This helps us evaluate our users‘ use of the web sites; compile statistical reports on activity; and improve our content and website performance.

Google Analytics gathers certain simple, non-personally identifying information over time, such as your IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring and exit pages, time stamp, and similar data about your use of the web sites. We do not link this information to any of your personal information such as your user name.

Apps on mobile devices

The mobile apps from Voice of God have access to various information on your device including personal information. This is only used as required for the app to function as you expect it to.

  * The app may require access to the Device ID which we use as a unique ID for that device.
  * The app may require access to Photos/Media/Files to store and play back sermons.
  * The app may require access to Wi-Fi to download or stream sermons that are not on your device.
  * In general, your privacy is important, so we treat your data as yours and do not access it unless it is required for the app to operate as you expect it to.

Anonymous Feedback on website

If you choose to leave feedback to one of our articles anonymously, it is truly anonymous, and we have no way of identifying you. We are therefore unable to respond to requests, or answer questions that are submitted anonymously.

Children‘s Online Privacy

We are concerned about the privacy of young children. We only collect the information necessary to enable them to participate in the YF activities we sponsor. We encourage all parents to become involved with their child‘s access to our site. We strongly encourage the parents of young children to access their child‘s YF account so they know the information that is stored there.

How we share the information that we collect

We do not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information with third parties

We do not disclose personal information outside Voice of God Recordings, unless such disclosure is necessary to comply with a court order, or to protect the safety and security of our other users.

Your privacy is our first consideration, so personal information **inside** VGR is limited to only those who need access to provide services to you.

We may share some basic User Personal Information with your permission, so we can perform services you have requested. _Examples: Our Church List, and Quiz Results. The church information is provided to us for the purpose of giving enquirers a list of local churches. Quiz Results that list your tape quiz scores are only posted if you allow it._

How Voice of God Recordings secures your information

VGR takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or destruction; maintain data accuracy; and help ensure the appropriate use of your personal information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.

No method of transmission, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have a question about our privacy policy please contact VGR at [privacy@branham.org](mailto:privacy@branham.org?subject=Privacy)
